mailstreet.com 2006-10-20

# MailStreet Exchange 2003 Hosting, Email Outsourcing using Microsoft Exchange 2003 Server. Outsource Corporate Email with MailStreet Hosted Exchange 2003 Email

Why MailStreet?

Why MailStreet?

Features and Benefits

Features and Benefits

Reliability and Performance

Reliability and Performance

Security and Privacy

Security and Privacy

How it Works

How it Works

Transitioning to MailStreet

Transitioning to MailStreet

Pricing Plans

Pricing Plans

Become a Reseller

Become a Reseller

Order Outlook 2003 CD

Order Outlook 2003 CD

Sign up Now | Free Trial

Sign up Now | Free Trial

Wireless Overview

Wireless Overview

Blackberry Enterprise Server

Blackberry Enterprise Server

GoodLink

GoodLink

Windows Mobile ActiveSync

Windows Mobile ActiveSync

Outlook Mobile Access

Outlook Mobile Access

|  |  | 

MailStreet takes your privacy very seriously.  Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**What This Privacy Policy Is About**

  * This policy will tell you how MailStreet handles personal information that MailStreet collects and receives, including information related to your usage, both past and present, of MailStreet products and services, including MailStreet. Personal information can be defined as information about you including your name, company name, address, email address, and/or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MailStreet does not own or manage, or to individuals that MailStreet does not employ, instruct, or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**   

  * MailStreet collects information when you register with MailStreet and/or MailStreet, when you use MailStreet products or services, and when you browse/visit MailStreet pages.
  * Upon registering, we ask for your name, email address, zip code. Once you have done this and sign in to our services, you are no longer anonymous to MailStreet.
  * MailStreet automatically receives and records information in our servers and on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, MailStreet cookie information, and the specific page you request. This information is not shared with any 3rd parties and is used only for internal technical and sales-tracking purposes.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * MailStreet does not rent, sell, auction-off, or share any personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies or entities, with the following exceptions: 
    * We have written permission to do so, or receive “electronic permission” via email or instant messaging, to do so.
    * Occasionally, MailStreet will seek testimonials from satisfied customers to serve as advertising for our services. This information will only be gathered with permission to do so, or when volunteered, or when MailStreet receives “electronic permission”, via email or instant-messaging, to do so.
    * We will respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
    * If required by law or license agreement to do so.
    * We find it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MailStreet's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    * We transfer information about you if MailStreet is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MailStreet will notify you before any information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Cookies**

  * MailStreet may set and access MailStreet cookies on your computer. 
  * Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Other companies do not have access to MailStreet's cookies.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**   
|  | General  
---|---  
  
  * You can edit your MailStreet Account Information at any time by sending an email to [support@mailstreet.com](mailto:support@mailstreet.com). 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MailStreet service, such as service announcements. Administrative messages are considered part of your MailStreet account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
  * You can delete your MailStreet account by sending an email to [support@mailstreet.com](mailto:support@mailstreet.com). 
  * You may choose to opt-out of marketing-related correspondence from MailStreet, such as the MailStreet Newsletter. We never share your email address or other personal information with any 3rd-party.
  * Some information may remain on file for deleted accounts for 30 days or more for accounting and other legal/licensing record-keeping.

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to your personal information to employees who need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
  * Your MailStreet account information is password-protected.
  * In certain areas MailStreet uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
  * MailStreet is not responsible for security issues related to users choosing “easy” passwords (i.e. “password”) or users who fail to safeguard their password.
  * MailStreet is not responsible for viruses and other “Trojan horse” programs running on customers’ PC that capture keystrokes or electronically detect users’ passwords.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * MailStreet may update this policy. We will notify you about changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MailStreet account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Questions and Suggestions**   
If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at [support@mailstreet.com](mailto:support@mailstreet.com).
